National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap298
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; 1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  - Adults, 1988-2006, Undated; 1.1; 9 cubic ft.
    - Christy, Lawrence (PA), 1992 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Clark, Andrew Bert (AL), 1994 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Clark, Douglas (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Clark, Herman Robert Jr. (TX) Executed December 6, 1994, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Clark, Jack (TX), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Clark, James Lee (TX), 1994 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Clark, Joseph L. (OH), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Clark, Richard Dean (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Clark, Ronald (PA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Clark, William John (CA), 1993 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Clayton, Robert (OK), 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Clemons, Reginald (MO), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Coble, Billie (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Cockrun, Johnny (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Coddington, Herbert (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Code, Nathaniel (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Coe, Robert (TN), 1999 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Coffman, Cynthia (CA), 1998; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Coldwell, Daniel (GA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Colella, Paul Richard (TX), 1992 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Coleman, Alton (OH), 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Coleman, Clydell (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Coleman, Russell (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Collins, Kenneth (MD), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Collins, Scott (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Colvin, Eugene S. (MD), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Colvin-El, Eugene (MD), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Comeaux, Adam (CA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Comer, Robert (AZ), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Conforti, Michael (PA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Conner, Kevin (IN), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Conklin, Robert (GA), 2005; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Cook, Daniel W. (AZ), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Cook, Derrick (OH), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Cook, Kerry (TX), 1991 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Cook, Robert (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Cooks, Cornel (OK), 1999 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Cooper, Carl (DC) [1 of 2], 2000; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Cooper, Carl (DC) [2 of 2], 2000; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Cooper, Gene Tony (SC), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Cooper, Kevin (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Cooper, Richard M. (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Copeland, Faye (MO), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Copeland, James (LA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Corcoran, Joseph (IN), 2005; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Cordova, Jorge (TX), 1998; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Corley, Edward Eldon (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Correll, Jerry W. (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Corwin, Daniel L. (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Coulter, Roger (AR), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Cousan, Donald (LA), 1994 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Cox, Donna (NC), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Cox, Michael (AR), 1993; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Cox, Tiequon (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Crane, Alvin Wayne (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Crawford, Charles (MS), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Crew, Mark, (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Crews, Paul David (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Crews, William (IL), 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Cross, Charles (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Cruse, William (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Cruz, Javier G. (TX), 1998; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Cruz, Rolando (IL), 2000; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Cudjo, Armenia (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Cummings, Raynard (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Cunningham, AL (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Cunningham, Clinton (OR), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Curl, Robert Zane (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - D'Amato, Joseph C. (PA), 1999 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Dalton, Kerry Lyn (CA), 1998 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Daniels, Henry "Butch" (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Daniels, Jackson (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Daniels, Michael (IN), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Danks, Joseph (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Davie, Roderick (OH), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Davis, Allen (FL), 1999; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Davis, Don (AR), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Davis, Gary (CO), 1997; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Davis, Girvies L. (IL) Executed May 7, 1995, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Davis, Gregory (MS), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Davis, James (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Davis, Jimmy (AL), 1994 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Davis, Kenneth (MS), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Davis, Ralph (MO), 1999 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Davis, Richard (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Davis, Stanley (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Davis, Thomas (SC), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Davis, William (TX), 1998 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Dawson, David (DE), 2001; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - DeBlanc, David (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - DeBruce, Derrick (AL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Deer, Ronald (CA), 1991; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - DeHoyos, Richard (CA), 1993; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - De La Cruz, Jose (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Delk, Monty (TX), 2002 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - DeLong, Wayne (VA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Dement, Ronnie (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Demps, Bennie (FL), 2000; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Dennis, Jimmy (PA), 1998; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Depew, Rhett (OH), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - DePriest, Timothy (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Deruise, Clifford (LA), 1996 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Detrich, David Scott (AZ), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Diaz, Angel (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Diaz, Robert (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Dickens, Gregory Scott (AZ), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Dickerson, Frederick (OH), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Dickey, Colin (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Dillbeck, Donald (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Dillingham, Jeffrey (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Djerf, Richard Kenneth (AZ), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Dobbs, Wiley (GA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Dodd, Westly Allan (WA), 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Doerr, Eugene (AZ), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Donald, Richard (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Douglas, Fred B. (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Down, Ernest (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Dowthitt, Dennis (TX), 1998; 2001 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Draughon, Martin (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Drayton, Leroy J. (SC), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Drew, Robert (TX) Executed August 22, 1994, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Drinkard, Richard (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Dubois, Johnile L. (VA) August 31, 1998, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Duckett, James A. (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Dudley, Marion Butler (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Duest, Llyod (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Dueffey, Steven (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Dunkle,Jon (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Dunn, Henry (TX), 2001 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Dunn, Kenneth (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Duren, David (AL), 1999; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Duvall, John (OK), 1998; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Dyer, Alfred (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Earhart, James (TX), 1999 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Earp, Ricky Lee (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Earvin, Harvey (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Eaton, Dennis N. (VA), 1998; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Eaton, Winthrop (LA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Echols, Damien (AR), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Eddmonos, Durlyn (IL), 1997; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Edelbacher, Peter (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Edwards, Thomas Francis (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Eldridge, Coerald Cornellus (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Elkins, Michael E. (SC) Executed June 12, 1997, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Elledge, William (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Elliott, John Williams (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Elliot, Joseph (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Elmore, Edward L. (SC), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Enmund, Earl (FL), 2002 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Epperson, Roger D. (KY), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Ervin, Thomas (MO), 2001; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Esparza, Gregory (OH), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Espinoza, Antonio (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Etheridge, Gary (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Evans, David L. (MS), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Evans, Vernon Lee (MD), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Fahy, Henry (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Farina, Anthony (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Farley, Richard (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Farr, Victor M. (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Farris, Troy (TX), 1998 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Fauber, Curtis Lynn (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Faulder, Stanley (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Faulkner, Arthur (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Felder Jr., Sammig (TX), 1999 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Felker, Ellis (GA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Ferguson, Cornelius (DE), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Ferrell, Dallas (SC), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Fields, Steve (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Fierro, Cesar (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Fierro, David Ray (CA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Fisher, David Lee (VA), 1999 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)
    - Fisher, James (OK), 1992 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)
    - Fisher, Robert (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
    - Fisher, Willie (NC), 2001 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 144)
    - Fleenor, D.H (IN), 1999; 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 145)
    - Fleming, Son (GA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 146)
    - Flores, Miguel Angel (TX), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 147)
    - Flowers, Wendell (NC), 1999; 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 148)
    - Fluke, Ronald (OK), 2001; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 149)
    - Foley, Robert (KY), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 150)
    - Ford, Alvin B. (FL), 2004; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 151)
    - Ford, Glen (LA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 152)
    - Ford, Kenneth (PA), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 153)
    - Ford, Pernell (AL), 1999; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 154)
    - Ford, Priscilla (NV), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 155)
    - Foster, Charles K. (FL), Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 156)
    - Foster, Charles (OK), 2000; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Foster, Emitt (MO), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Foster, Lafonda (KY), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Foster, Richard (TX), 2000 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Fotopoulos, Konstantinos (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Fowler, Mark (OK), 2000 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Fox, Billy-Ray, 2000 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Frank, Leo (GA), 1996 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Frank, Theodore (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Freeman, David (AL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Fretwell, Bobby (AR), 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Frey, Roderick (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Frierson, Lavell (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Fry, Anthony (VA), 1998 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Fuller, Aaron (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Fuller, Throne (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Fulminante. Oreste (AZ), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Gall, William Eugene (KY), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Gallamore, Samuel Clark (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Gallego, Gerald (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Garceau, Robert Frederick (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Garcia, Fernando (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Garcia, Guineuere (IL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Garcia, Gustavo (TX), 1991 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Garcia, Hector Torres (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Garcia, Randy Eugene (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Gardner, David (TX), 1998 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Gardner, Mark (AR), 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Garner, William Lee (OH), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Gay, Kenneth (CA), 1993; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Gay, Yvette (NC), 1991; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Gentry, Kenneth (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Giarratano, Joseph (VA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Gibbs, David (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Gibson, Ronald (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Gilbert, Larry (SC), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Gilliam, Burley (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Gilliam, Jr., Tyrone (MD), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Gilies, Jesse (AZ), 1998 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Gladney, George Nathaniel Jr. (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Gleaton, J.D (SC), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Glen, Robert (TN), 2005 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Glock, Robert (FL), 2000; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Goff, David Lee (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Goins, Christopher (VA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Gollehon, William (MT), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Gonzales, Jesse (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Goodman, Spencer (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Goodwin, Alvin (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Gorby, Thomas (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Gordon, Patrick (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Gore, David A. (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Gosch, Lesley Lee (TX), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Goss, Cornelius Alan (TX), 2000 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Goynes, Theodore (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Graham, Andre (VA), 1999 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Graham, Harrison (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Grandison, Anthony (MD), 1994; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Gray, Mario (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Gray, Marlin (MO), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Gray, Ronald (Military), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Green, Alphonso (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Green, Anthony (SC), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Green, Harvey (NC), 1999 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Green, Norman (TX), 1999 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Green, Ricky (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Greene, Beau John (AZ), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Greene, Jack (AR), 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Gregory, Wilson (KY), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Gretzler, Douglas (AZ), 1998 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Gribble, Lane (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Gribble, Timothy (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Griffin, Donald (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Griffin, Larry (MO), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Griffin, Michael (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Griffin, Milton (MO), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Griffin, Rodney (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Groseclose, Bill (TN), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Grossman, Martin (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Guerra, Jose Francisco (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Guerra, Ricardo Aldape (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Gulbrandson, David (AZ), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Gunsby, Donald (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Gutierrez, Isaac (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Gutierrez, Joe Angel (TX), 1994 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Guy, Joe (TX) Stay Granted June 28, 2000, 1994; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Hasg, Ranoy (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Hackett, Richard D. (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Hafdahl, Randall (TX), 2001; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Haight, Rany (KY), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Haley, Kevin (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Haliburton, Jerry (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Hall, Dennis (GA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Hall, Freddie Lee (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Hall, Orlando C. (AK), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Hall, Steven Wayne (AL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Hallford, Phillip (AL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Hameen, Abdullah T. (OK), 2001 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Hamilton, Bernard (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Hamilton, Billy Ray (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Hamilton, Marcus (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Hamilton, Michael (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Hammer, David Paul (FED), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Hammond, Jerry (AL), 1995; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Hampton, Lloyd W. (IL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Haney, Judy (AL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Hannibal, Sheldon (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Hansen, Tracy A. (MS), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Harden, Donald Eugene (AZ) Executed April 6, 1992, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Hardwick, John Gary (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Harries, Ron (TN), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Harris III, Benjamin J. (WA), 2005 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Harris, David (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Harris, George B. (MO), 2000; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Harris, James A. (IN), 2005 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Harris, Kenneth Bernard (TX) Executed June 3, 1997, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Harris, Louise (AL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Harvey Jr. Harold Lee (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Haskett, Randy (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Hatch, Steven (OK), 1996 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Hawkins, Jeffrey (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Hawkins, Samuel (TX) Executed February 21, 1995, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Hawkins, Thomas (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Hays, Henry F. (AL), 1997; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Heath, Ronald P. (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Hedlund, Michael (AZ), 2002; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Heidnik, Gary (PA), 1997; 1999; 2005; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Heiselbetz, Earl (TX), 1999 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Heishman, Harvey Lee (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Henderson, Jerome (OH), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Henderson, Jerry Paul (AL), 2005 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Henderson, Wilbur A. (AR), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Henry, John (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Henry, Robert L. (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Henry, Josoph (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Herman, David Lee (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Hernandez, Francis (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Hernandez, Rodolfo (TX), 2002 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Herrera, William Sr. (AZ), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Hicks, David (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Hill, Clarence E. (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)
    - Hill, Darrel (AR), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)